Hello friends, welcome to my YouTube channel.
We are now in results season week two
where around 36 companies will be seen disclosing their quarter 4
numbers.
So let's see.  As you
know, the Q4 season lasts a bit longer.   From
around 28th to 29th March, you will see
companies showing their results here.
So let's see which
companies will show their numbers on which date.
So, if we talk about 13th April i.e. Monday, then on
Monday, about seven
companies will be seen disclosing their quarter four numbers.
So
let's see some of those names like jd ICIC
Pension AMC i.e. ICIC PDL Asset
Management Company, Swaraj Engine Innovation,
Inprises ind Bank Housing and
Continental Controls, you will see the numbers of all these
coming on Monday.
So let's talk about 14th April i.e.
Tuesday.  So on Tuesday, we will see
around seven companies disclosing their Quarter 4
numbers.
So let's look at some of their names.
ICIC Pidenial Life Insurance Company,
Novaco Vistas Day Network, Imcon Havey Bhavani,
Kapil Raj Finance and Anant Rathi Shares &
Stock Broker, you will
see the numbers of all these coming on 14th.  So
let's move on to Wednesday, the 15th. On
Wednesday, we will see around nine companies
disclosing their quarter 4 numbers.  Let's
look at some of their names.  ICIC LBT, HDb Finance, Ekon
Engineering, Reliance Infra, GTPL
Hathway, SPL, Semiconductor, Tejas
Networks, Lotus Chocolate and Media
Matrix.  So you will see the numbers of all these big companies
coming on the 15th.
So let's talk about the 16th i.e.
Thursday.  So on Thursday, we will see
around eight companies disclosing their Q4
numbers.
Some of them look like big names.
So you will see the numbers of IT sector giant
Wipro coming on Thursday.
Along with this,
you will get to see the numbers of all these big companies like HDFC, HDFC AMC i.e. HDFC Assist Management Company, Crisil, VST Industries, AOK Industries and USG Finserv on Thursday.
So if we talk about 17th April i.e.
Friday, then on Friday
you will see the numbers of only two companies coming.
Mastek and Havecable.
So if we talk about 18th April i.e. Saturday, then on
Saturday
you will see the numbers of about three companies coming.   So,
you will see the numbers of these three big banks of the banking sector, HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank and Yes Bank, coming here on Saturday.  If we
talk about 19th April i.e. Sunday, then
you will not see the number of any company coming on Sunday.
So friends, if you have
not subscribed to our channel yet,
then subscribe to the channel so that
you do not miss any result related update.
Along with this, every week,
you will get the exact result analysis of all the big companies that will disclose their quarter four numbers on this channel and
every Saturday, you will get the
video of the company that will disclose the results the next week on
this channel.  So if you have
not subscribed to our channel
then do subscribe to the channel.  Also, if you
like the video then please like it.